{
    "subject": "resource/Hot_Rod_Circuit",
    "predicate": "property/origin",
    "object": "resource/Auburn,_Alabama",
    "human_readable": "The origin of Hot Rod Circuit is Auburn, Alabama.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9300643801689148,
            "question": "What city in Alabama is the origin of Hot Rod Circuit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8961256742477417,
            "question": "Is Hot Rod Circuit from Alabama?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8180222511291504,
            "question": "Where did Hot Rod Circuit originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7518595457077026,
            "question": "What is the state of origin for Hot Rod Circuit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6936904788017273,
            "question": "In which city was Hot Rod Circuit founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6010134816169739,
            "question": "Where did Hot Rod Circuit first emerge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3287229537963867,
            "question": "What US state is associated with Hot Rod Circuit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2958306670188904,
            "question": "Auburn, Alabama is known for which musical group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27460068464279175,
            "question": "Hot Rod Circuit's roots lie in which place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.259672075510025,
            "question": "Can you tell me the birthplace of Hot Rod Circuit?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The origin of Hot Rod Circuit is Auburn, Alabama.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3705_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hot Rod Circuit's roots lie in which place?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3705_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Auburn, Alabama is known for which musical group?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3705_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What US state is associated with Hot Rod Circuit?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3705_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3705_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3705_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3705_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3705_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3705_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3705_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3705_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3705_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3705_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3705_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the triple:\n\n* Document 1 and 3 mention \"Auburn, Alabama\" as the hometown/band's origin of Hot Rod Circuit.\n* Document 7 (infobox) also mentions \"Origin = Auburn, Alabama\".\n* There is no conflicting information provided in any of the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"Hot Rod Circuit were an indie rock/rock band from Auburn, Alabama established in 1999,\" which supports the statement that their origin is Auburn, Alabama."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}